Isn't it beautiful!
是不是很漂亮？
- Oh, my word. What a wonderful sight!
- Fantastic!
- 噢，天啊，多美的景象!  - 壮观！
Listen, will you two stop gaping at that
and get us out of here.
嘿，你俩能不能别感慨了，带我们离开这里
Don't worry, Jamie. We're safe in the Tardis.
别担心, Jamie, 我们在 TARDIS 里面很安全
Are you sure? Has the Tardis
ever been buried in lava before?
你确定吗？ TARDIS 被岩浆掩埋过没有？
- No.
- How can you be so sure we're going to be all right?
- 没有  - 那你怎么能这么肯定我们会没事？
Oh, dear.
噢, 亲爱的
- Is something wrong?
- This has happened before.
- 有什么不对劲吗？  - 这事儿以前也出现过
The fluid links aren't able to take the load. Oh!
流体连接器不工作了．噢！
(ZOE) Mercury vapour!
水银蒸汽！
Oh! This darn thing's stuck! Of all the stupid, idiotic!
噢！这个破玩意儿卡住了！最愚蠢、傻蛋！
- Doctor, The lava's up to the Tardis!
- (ZOE) Doctor
- 博士, 熔岩都快到 TARDIS 了!  - 博士
If only I could unstick this stupid, idiotic...
There we are.
只要我能挪动这个愚蠢、傻蛋的...这下好了
Have you done it? Are we on our way?
你搞定了吗？我们上路了？
It's stopped the fluid links from vaporising.
We shan't suffocate.
流体连接器停止蒸发了。我们不会窒息了
If we don't hurry, we'll be fried by the lava.
如果我们不快点, 就会被熔岩烧成灰了
- Isn't there any way we can get away?
- Well, there IS an emergency unit, but...
- 我们有什么可能逃脱吗？  - 唔, 是有一个紧急设备, 但是...
- I can't possibly use that.
- But this IS an emergency!
- 我不能启用那个  - 但是这就是紧急情况啊
But it moves the Tardis out of the
time-space dimension, out of reality!
但它会把 TARDIS 移出时空维度, 推到现实之外去！
Fine. Reality's getting too hot, anyway!
很好．反正现实已经太热了！
Oh, all right.
噢, 好吧
Here we are.
来看看
Now, then, which end was...?
喏, 哪头是...
Yes...
对了
I can't possibly use this.
We don't know what will happen.
我不能启用这个, 我们不知道可能发生什么!
Stop your jabbering and get on with it. Look!
别叨叨了, 赶紧动手吧．看！